# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)


Blackcard.create([
  {
    question: "Why can't I sleep at night?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "I got 99 problems but _ ain't one.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What's a girl's best friend?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What's that smell?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "This is the way the world ends / This is the way the world ends / Not with a bang but with _.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is Batman's guilty pleasure?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "TSA guidelines now prohibit _ on airplanes.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What ended my last relationship?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "MTV's new reality show features eight washed-up celebrities living with _.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "I drink to forget _.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What's that sound?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What's the next Happy Meal&reg; toy?",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "It's a pity that kids these days are all getting involved with _.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "In the new Disney Channel Original Movie, Hannah Montana struggles with _ for the first time.",
    pick: 1
  },
  {
    question: "_. That's how I want to die.",
    pick: 1
  }
  ])


Whitecard.create([
  {
     answer: "Coat hanger abortions."
   },
  {
    answer:"Man meat."
  },
  {
    answer:"Autocannibalism."
  },
  {
     answer:"Vigorous jazz hands."
  },

  {
     answer:"Flightless birds."
  },
  {
     answer:"Pictures of boobs."
  },
  {
     answer:"Doing the right thing."
  },
  {
     answer:"The violation of our most basic human rights."
  },
  {
     answer:"Viagra&reg;."
  },
  {
     answer:"Self-loathing."
  },
  {
     answer:  "Spectacular abs."
  },
  {
     answer:  "A balanced breakfast."
  },
  {
     answer:  "Roofies."
  },
  {
     answer:   "Concealing a boner."
  },
  {
     answer:   "Amputees."
  },
  {
     answer:    "The Big Bang."
  },
  {
     answer:   "Former President George W. Bush."
  }
])
